{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: down", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["on", "a", "jungle", "down"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: awakened", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["the", "mouse", "awakened", "and"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["up", "of", "lion", "running"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: his", "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive pronoun.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["the", "his", "to", "This"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["the", "him", "when", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "paw", "the", "big"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lion", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["lion", "placed", "swallow", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["mouse", "little", "and", "Once"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: huge", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "This soon awakened the lion , who placed his huge paw on the mouse , and opened his big jaws to swallow him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["This", "paw", "huge", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: when", "question": "In the following sentence identify Wh-adverb.", "comprehension": "Once when a lion , the king of the jungle , was asleep , a little mouse began running up and down on him . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["asleep", "down", "jungle", "when"]}], "success": 1}
